<resources>

    <string name="local_type">en</string>
    <string name="err1">Cannot recognize standard solutions</string>
    <string name="err2">Please wait for a stable reading before pressing ENT</string>
    <string name="err3">Readings being unstable for a long time</string>
    <string name="err4"> pH Electrode zero potential of pH probe out of range（&lt;60mV or>60mV）</string>
    <string name="err5">Slope of pH probe out of range（&lt;85% or >110%）</string>
    <string name="err6">Time to perform calibration</string>
    <string name="fix1">1.     Please fully immerse the probe into calibration solution.\n
2.     The first point of calibration must be pH 7.00.\n
3.     Please check if the calibration solution is good – not expired or contaminated\n
4.     Please check if the probe is damaged (e.g. broken glass sensor or a crack on the sensor). If so, please replace the probe.\n
5.     The glass sensor or junction of the probe could get contaminated severely. Please use a soft brush dipped with soap water to clean the probe, then rinse it with purified water, and soak it in 3M KCL for 24 hours before use again.\n
6.     For other problems, please contact us at 614-285-3080 or info@aperainst.com\n</string>
    <string name="fix2">None. Wait for the smiley face to come up and stay on screen, then press ENT</string>
    <string name="fix3">1.     Please check if there is any air bubble inside the glass bulb sensor. If so, please shake the meter with force for several times to remove the air bubble(s).\n
2.     Please check if the probe is damaged (e.g. broken glass sensor or a crack on the sensor). If so, please replace the probe.\n
3.     The glass bulb sensor or junction of the probe could get contaminated severely. Please use a soft brush dipped with soap water to clean the probe, then rinse it with purified water, and soak it in 3M KCL for 24 hours before use again.\n
4.     The probe could be severely aged (response time is significantly slow; used for over 1 year). Please replace the probe.\n
5. This tester is not suitable for testing your sample. Please contact us to find a proper model most suitable for your application.\n
6.     For other problems, please contact us at 614-285-3080 or info@aperainst.com</string>
    <string name="fix4">1.     Check if the standard series setup in the pH parameter setting is consistent with the calibration solutions’(U.S.A standard is 4.00, 7.00, 10.01; NIST standard is 4.00, 6.86, 9.18)\n
2.     Check if the calibration solutions got expired or contaminated.\n
3.     Please check if the probe is damaged (e.g. broken glass sensor or a crack on the sensor). If so, please replace the probe.\n
4.     Electrode invalidated (Error 4 or Error 5 show up consistently after calibration while the above 3 problems are excluded). Please replace the electrode;\n
5.     The probe could be severely aged (response time is significantly slow; used for over 1 year). Please replace the probe；\n
6.     For other problems, please contact us at 614-285-3080 or info@aperainst.com\n</string>
    <string name="fix5">@string/fix4</string>
    <string name="fix6">Please enter calibration mode and perform calibration; or enter general settings to cancel the calibration reminder.</string>
</resources>
